let question = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "A tool used to organize, store, retrieve, and communicate groups of related information :",
        answer: "Database",
        option: [
            "Big Data",
            "Word",
            "Database",
            "Presentations"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 2,
        question: "The four main objects of a relational database consist of :",
        answer: "Form, table, query, report",
        option: [
            "Form, table, database, query, report",
            "Form, table, query, report",
            "Form, column, row, report",
            "Form, sort, table, query"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 3,
        question: "I can perform an advanced search. I am very similar to asking a detailed question :",
        answer: "Query",
        option: [
            "Table",
            "Report",
            "Form",
            "Query"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 4,
        question: "Arrange information in alphabetical/sequential order, A-Z, least to greatest, 1-10 :",
        answer: "Ascend",
        option: [
            "Data",
            "Descend",
            "Ascend",
            "Table"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 5,
        question: "If I am placed between terms I will retrieve data that contain both of the terms. Which connector am I? Example: candy ____ soda :",
        answer: "And",
        option: [
            "Not",
            "Or",
            "And",
            "But"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT an example of a database? ",
        answer: "DVD",
        option: [
            "Online library card catalog",
            "Real Estate listing",
            "Telephone book",
            "DVD"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 7,
        question: "Rows are called : ",
        answer: "Records",
        option: [
            "Fields",
            "Records",
            "Entry",
            "Table"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 8,
        question: "Columns are called : ",
        answer: "Fields",
        option: [
            "Table",
            "Fields",
            "Entry",
            "Rows"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 9,
        question: "Primary key in its parent table, but is included as an attribute in another host table : ",
        answer: "Foreign Key",
        option: [
            "Primary Key",
            "Foreign Key",
            "Alternate Key",
            "Composite Key"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 10,
        question: "Basically the SELECT command falls into the command category :",
        answer: "DML",
        option: [
            "DDL",
            "DML",
            "DDML",
            "DCL"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 11,
        question: "'ALTER TABLE mhs DROP PRIMARY KEY' The syntax above has a function for ",
        answer: "Deleting Primary Key",
        option: [
            "Changing data type",
            "Set Primary Key",
            "Deleting Primary Key",
            "Enter new data"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 12,
        question: "Is a command used to group some data in the SELECT command. Is the meaning of ",
        answer: "Group By",
        option: [
            "Having",
            "Aggregate",
            "Group By",
            "Where"
        ]
    }
]